Women's Action Alliance Records, 1970-1996
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES I. ADMINISTRATION 1971-96
  - Staff, 1976-83
    - General
      - Office supplies: correspondence and invoices (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Open House, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Pension plan (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Rolodex cards, undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Intra-office communication: notes and memoranda, 1972-89, undated (Box 44, Folder 1-11)
    - Meeting minutes, general, 1976-82, 1987-88 (Box 44-45, Folder 12-14)
    - Meeting minutes, program staff, 1979-80 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Personnel
      - Applications for employment (blank), undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Employee handbook material, 1993, undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Job descriptions, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Job search mailing list, undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Outreach contacts, undated (Box 45, Folder 9-10)
      - Resumes (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Retreat, 1976, undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Summer interns and student workers: correspondence, application materials, and miscellany, 1973-87, undated (Box 45, Folder 13-18)
      - Volunteers (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - Evaluation forms (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence and memoranda (Box 46, Folder 1)
      [restricted]
    - Evaluations (Box 46, Folder 2-4)
    - Salaries (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Terminations and resignations (Box 46, Folder 6-9)
    - Policy development (includes policy statements), 1976-80, undated (Box 47, Folder 1-8)
    - Project directors: minutes and memoranda, 1976-80, undated (Box 47, Folder 9-10)
  - Financial records
    - Financial statements and audits
      - Correspondence, 1978-81 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Statements and audit reports, 1972-94 (Box 47, Folder 12-15)
      - Supporting material: drafts, balance sheets, statements and CPA agreements, 1980-89 (Box 47, Folder 16-18)
    - Budget information
      - General: budgets and budget projections, cash flow statements, financial worksheets, notes, 1972-94 (Box 48, Folder 1-12)
      - Complete budget books, 1975-77 (Box 49, Folder 1-5)
    - Income
      - Account information, 1979, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Grant income, 1984-85 (Box 49, Folder 7)
        [for 1971-73, see budget book for 1977]
      - Royalty reports, 1977-82 (Box 49, Folder 8-10)
      - Savings passbooks, "Access to Equality," 1982 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Tax forms, 1971-73 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Tax return correspondence, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - Miscellany (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Development and fundraising
    - Consultants: legal and general correspondence, contracts, audits, notes, plans and reports, 1983-96, undated (Box 50, Folder 1-10)
    - Copywriter Julienne Berk: resume and samples, circa 1971 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence and memoranda
      - Development Coordinator Sally Li Young, 1980-84 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Director of Development Donna L. Meade, 1978-79, 1980, 1988-89, undated (Box 50, Folder 13-14)
      - General (e.g. letters from donors re: grants and contributions), 1973, 1987-88 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - Mailing lists, 1993-96 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
      - Outreach (mass mailings), 1983 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Search for development officer, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Subjects
      - A-E (includes Donna Meade's memoranda) (Box 51, Folder 5-21)
      - F-R (Box 52, Folder 1-25)
      - R-W (includes the following Research materials: "Inequality of Sacrifice: The Impact of the Reagan Budget on Women": report, 1982; "The Women's Movement and Foundations": transcript of a 17 September 1971 symposium with Brenda Feigen Fasteau, Marjorie Fine, Eleanor Holmes Norton, and Gloria Steinem; and Yankelovish, Skelly & White, Inc: "The Public Policy Climate," 1982) (Box 53, Folder 1-18)
    - Fundraising
      - Campaigns: contribution and donor lists, proposals, mailing lists, and direct mail tabulations, 1972-88, 1995-96 (Box 54-56)
      - Benefits and events (Box 56, Folder 13-16)
        - Theater events: reservation and attendance lists, contribution records, correspondence, playbills, clippings, and financial records, (includes Wendy Wasserstein to Gloria Steinem correspondence) 1979-89 (Box 57, Folder 17-21)
        - Women's Roasts
          [see also SERIES IV. PHOTOGRAPHS]
          - Geraldine Ferraro: clippings, invitation, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 1)
          - Liz Smith: invitation, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 2)
          - Donna Shalala: invitation, bills and expenses, correspondence, clippings, and miscellany, 1987) (Box 58, Folder 3-12)
          - Pat Schroeder, 1988
            - Invitation, correspondence, checks and invoices, lists, and notes (Box 58, Folder 13-20)
            - Miscellany, photographs, programs, publicity, silent auction, and final report (Box 59, Folder 1-6)
        - Museum of Folk Art fundraiser and quilt auction: donor and attendee list, miscellany, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 7-8)
        - A Celebration of Leadership in Action: invitation, awardees, press release, program packet and miscellany, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 9-16)
        - Funders, arranged alphabetically (Box 60-76)
        - Proposals, 1971-85, 1993, n.d. (Box 77-78)
- SERIES II. PROJECTS 1972-96
  - Economics
    - Economic Development Project, 1980-84
      - Administrative
        - Concept and plan (Box 79, Folder 1)
        - Summary (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Advisory committee (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence
        - General (Box 79, Folder 4)
        - Maddy Lee (Box 79, Folder 5)
        - Stephanie Smith, National Economic Development and Law Center, 1984 (includes notes and Sara Gould's manuscript for the Law Center Report) (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - Financial: budgets, receipts and bills, 1982-84 (Box 79, Folder 7-9)
      - Development
        - Budgets and proposals (Box 79, Folder 10-14)
        - Proposals and research materials (Box 80, Folder 1-4)
      - Memoranda (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - Minutes, undated (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Miscellany (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - Project Director Sara Gould (Box 80, Folder 8-9)
      - Struggling Through Tight Times: A Handbook for Women's and Other Non-Profit Organizations, 1984: drafts, manuscript, and research materials (Box 80, Folder 10-14)
      - Survey: "Income Generation by Women's Social Service Organizations:" correspondence, notes, questionnaires, and workplan (Box 81, Folder 1-5)
      - Conferences and travel (Box 81, Folder 6-15)
      - Fundraising (Box 81, Folder 16-18)
      - Foundation fundraising (Box 82, Folder 1-2)
      - Income generation: proposals and research (Box 82, Folder 3-5)
      - Groups
        - Carasa, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 6)
        - Casa Myrna Vasquez, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 7)
        - CHART, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 8)
        - Chrysalis (Madison, WI), 1983 (Box 82, Folder 9)
        - Coalition for Abused Women, 1983? (Box 82, Folder 10)
        - Good Neighbor Settlement House, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 11)
        - Knoxville Women's Center, 1982-84 (Box 82, Folder 12-13)
        - Mothers of Many (MOM), 1983 (Box 82, Folder 14)
        - Mountain Women's Exchange, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 15)
        - Ms. Foundation for Women, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 16)
        - National Congress of Neighborhood Women, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 17)
        - National Institute for Women of Color, undated (Box 82, Folder 18)
        - Older Women's League, 1983-84 (Box 82, Folder 19)
        - Project Greenhope, 1983-84 (Box 82, Folder 20)
        - Single Parent Resource Center, 1981-83 (Box 82, Folder 21)
        - Women's Equity Program, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 22)
        - Women's Foundation, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 23)
        - Women's Funding Coalition, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 24)
        - Women's Institute for Housing and Economic Development, 1982-83 (Box 82, Folder 25)
        - Working Women's Education Fund, 1983-84 (Box 82, Folder 26)
      - Resources
        - A-F (Box 82, Folder 27-29)
        - G-Z (Box 83, Folder 1-10)
    - Non-Traditional Occupations for Women
      - General: interviews summaries and notes of women with non-traditional occupations, program evaluations, newsletters, and printed material, 1977-84, undated (Box 83, Folder 11-14)
      - Programs
        - Women's Enterprises of Boston, Project Quality, 1979
          - Articles of agreement, proposals, and reports (Box 83, Folder 15-17)
          - Questionnaires, interview guidelines, and workshop plans (Box 84, Folder 1-2)
        - Dept. of Health Education and Welfare, Development of an Outreach Program to Attract Women Into Male-Intensive Vocational Education Programs: proposal and related materials, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 3-7)
      - Survey, 1979-80
        - Administration: evaluation, intake and assessment, placement, planning, recruitment, and training materials (Box 84, Folder 8-15)
        - Responses (organized alphabetically by state) 1979-80 (Box 84-87)
      - Publications
        - Jo Sanders, The Nuts and Bolts of Non-Traditional Occupations: How to Help Women Enter Non- Traditional Occupations 1986 (Box 87, Folder 6-7)
        - Constance Drake Cauley, Time for a Change: A Woman's Guide to Non-Traditional Occupations 1981 (Box 87, Folder 8)
        - Distribution information (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Women at Work Expositions
      - 1978 Expo
        - Administration: correspondence, memoranda and miscellany (Box 87, Folder 10-15)
          [see also OVERSIZE for posters]
        - Fundraising
          - General and correspondence (Box 87, Folder 16-17)
          - Mailing lists and reports (Box 88, Folder 1-3)
        - Planning: correspondence and memoranda, reservation forms, schedules, workshop descriptions (Box 88, Folder 5-16)
        - Publicity: correspondence and agreement with Public Interest Public Relations, media packet, printed material (Box 88, Folder 17-19)
        - Publicity: clippings (Box 89, Folder 1)
        - Feedback and follow-up: critiques and complaints, panelist notes, questionnaires (Box 89, Folder 2-6)
      - 1979 Expo
        [see also SERIES V. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIAL]
        - Administration: correspondence, memoranda, mailing list, proposal, and financial material (Box 89, Folder 7-15)
        - Fundraising: correspondence, funder worksheets (Box 90, Folder 1-6)
        - Planning
          - General and notes (Box 90, Folder 7-8)
          - Correspondence, memoranda, registration materials, schedules, and miscellany (Box 91, Folder 1-13)
        - Workshop planning
          - Access to credit and venture capital (Box 91, Folder 14)
          - Alternative Work Schedules (Box 91, Folder 15)
          - Apprenticeships and Vocational Education (Box 91, Folder 16)
          - Benefits (Box 91, Folder 17)
          - Changing careers (Box 92, Folder 1)
          - Changing personal values (Box 92, Folder 2)
          - Child care (Box 92, Folder 3)
          - Education (Box 92, Folder 4)
          - EEO and Affirmative action, I & II (Box 92, Folder 5)
          - Entering the workplace (Box 92, Folder 6)
          - Equal pay (Box 92, Folder 7)
          - Funding women's programs (Box 92, Folder 8)
          - Hazardous substances (Box 92, Folder 9)
          - Images of women (Box 92, Folder 10)
          - Recruitment (Box 92, Folder 11)
          - Sexual harassment (Box 92, Folder 12)
          - Sharing limited resources (Box 92, Folder 13)
          - New woman as consumer (Box 92, Folder 14)
          - Upward mobility (Box 92, Folder 15)
          - Upward mobility for secretaries (Box 92, Folder 16)
          - Women and labor (Box 92, Folder 17)
          - Women as directors (Box 92, Folder 18)
          - Women as managers (Box 92, Folder 19)
          - Women's groups in the workplace (Box 92, Folder 20)
          - Wonder women at work (Box 92, Folder 21)
          - Working and parenting (Box 92, Folder 22)
          - Working couples (Box 92, Folder 23)
        - Proceedings: transcripts
          - Opening remarks and welcome, Ruth J. Abram (Box 92, Folder 24)
          - A Capital Idea (Box 92, Folder 25)
          - Boss Ladies (Box 92, Folder 26)
          - Calling the Shots (Box 92, Folder 27)
          - Changing Careers in Midstream (Box 92, Folder 28)
          - Couples and Conflict (Box 92, Folder 29)
          - Displaced Homemakers (Box 92, Folder 30)
          - EEO in the Affirmative, I & II (Box 92, Folder 31)
          - Equal Pay (Box 92, Folder 32)
          - From Mother Jones (Box 92, Folder 33)
          - Hand Off! (Box 92, Folder 34)
          - Is 9-5 Good for Business? (Box 92, Folder 35)
          - Marketing Patterns (Box 92, Folder 36)
          - Making It (Box 92, Folder 37)
          - Making Pipe Dreams Come True (Box 92, Folder 38)
          - Making the Job Safe (Box 92, Folder 39)
          - Mirror Mirror (Box 92, Folder 40)
          - Peanut Butter and Policy (Box 92, Folder 41)
          - Power of Susan B. Anthony's Dollar (Box 92, Folder 42)
          - Raises not Roses (Box 93, Folder 1)
          - Recruitment (Box 93, Folder 2)
          - Remarks, P.C. Krist (Box 93, Folder 3)
          - Rocking the Cradle (Box 93, Folder 4)
          - A Woman's Voice in the Workplace (Box 93, Folder 5)
          - Women in the Equation (Box 93, Folder 6)
          - Wonder Women (Box 93, Folder 7)
        - Publicity: fact sheets, media packet and printed material (Box 93, Folder 8-10)
        - Feedback and follow-up: drafts, conference report (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Education
    - Children of Single Parents in the Schools
      - Administration: correspondence, phone logs, financial records, proposals, 1987-88 (Box 93, Folder 12-18)
      - Interviews
        - General and correspondence (Box 93, Folder 19-20)
        - Focus groups: correspondence, data sheets, interview summaries, notes, 1988
          - General, set-up, and statistics (Box 93, Folder 21-23)
          - Children (Box 93, Folder 24)
          - Day Camps (Box 93, Folder 25)
          - Parents (Box 94, Folder 1)
            [see also audiotapes in SERIES V. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIAL]
          - Single mothers (includes divorced/separated, widowed and never-married) (Box 94, Folder 2)
          - Teachers (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Project files: newsletters, brochures, publications, and other printed materials, circa 1988 (Box 94, Folder 4-26)
      - Subjects
        - General (Box 94, Folder 27)
        - A-Z (includes Divorce and Separation; Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974; Never- married women; Non-custodial parents) (Box 95, Folder 1-12)
      - Margaret Barnwell Hargreaves: research material (includes bibliographies, note cards, articles, abstracts, unpublished papers), draft materials, and publication, Learning Under Stress: Children of Single Parents and the Schools, 1991 (Box 95-100)
    - Institute on Women's History, 1979
      - Administration
        - Artists, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 1)
        - Bibliography, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 2)
        - Book Project (fund), 1979 (Box 101, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, 1978-80 (Box 101, Folder 4-8)
        - Evaluations, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 9-12)
        - Evening program, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 13)
        - Faculty resumes, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 14)
        - Films, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 15)
        - Greyhound Bus and Hotel Washington, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 16)
        - Institute description, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 17)
        - Institute projects, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 18)
        - Institute schedule/Sarah Lawrence College Summer, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 19)
        - Lilly endowment: correspondence, report, 1979-80 (Box 102, Folder 1-4)
        - Mailings, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 5-6)
        - Meetings (includes Gerda Lerner, Ruth J. Abram), 1979 (Box 102, Folder 7-9)
        - Opening lecture, July 16, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 10)
        - Proposal, n.d (Box 102, Folder 11)
        - Report to the leadership of national women's organizations, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 12)
        - Sarah Lawrence College Housing Plan (Box 102, Folder 13)
        - Scholarships, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 14)
        - Selected students - tentative list, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 15)
        - Sisterships, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 16)
        - Smithsonian notes, 1978-79 (Box 102, Folder 17-18)
        - Women of color panel/outreach, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 19)
        - Women who could not attend, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 20)
      - Financial: budgets, correspondence, expense reports, 1978-79 (Box 102, Folder 21-24)
      - Publicity
        - Agenda Magazine, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 25)
        - Awards breakfast: correspondence, notes, press release, and speeches by Gerda Lerner and Ruth Abram, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 26-28)
        - Congressional Record, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 29)
        - Correspondence, 1978-79 (Box 102, Folder 30-31)
        - Press clippings (includes Ms. and Vogue), 1979 (Box 102, Folder 32-33)
        - PIPR (Public Interest Public Relations), 1979 (Box 103, Folder 1-2)
        - Smithsonian ceremony: correspondence and press statement, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 3)
        - Participants, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 4-41)
      - Women's History Week, 1979-80
        - General (Box 103, Folder 42)
        - Correspondence (Box 103, Folder 43)
        - Campaigns (congressional and presidential) (Box 103, Folder 44-45)
        - Handouts (Box 104, Folder 1)
        - Images (Box 104, Folder 2)
        - New York City organizing: correspondence, 1979 (Box 104, Folder 3)
        - Outreach: women's organizations (Box 104, Folder 4)
        - Press conference: correspondence, releases, and address by Gerda Lerner, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 5)
        - Printed material, circa 1984-85 (Box 104, Folder 6)
        - Proclamations (Box 104, Folder 7)
        - Resolution with signatures (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Non-Sexist Child Development Project
      - Administration
        - Correspondence
          - General, 1972-82 (Box 104-111)
          - Subjects
            - Colleges and universities, 1973-75 (Box 111, Folder 9-11)
            - Community centers, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 12)
            - Day care centers, 1973-74 (Box 111, Folder 13)
            - Government, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 14)
            - Hospitals, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 15)
            - Libraries, 1973-74 (Box 112, Folder 1)
            - Organizations: includes teacher and other organizations, 1973-74 (Box 112, Folder 2-3)
            - Parents magazine, 1978 (Box 112, Folder 4)
            - Publishing companies, 1973-74 (Box 112, Folder 5)
            - Religious groups, 1973-74 (Box 112, Folder 6)
            - Review requests, 1976-77 (Box 112, Folder 7)
            - Schools, 1973-74 (Box 112, Folder 8-9)
            - Social development, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 10)
            - Technical assistance, 1978-79 (Box 112, Folder 11)
            - Women's groups, 1973-74 (Box 112, Folder 12)
        - Flow chart and timeline, 1979-81 (Box 112, Folder 13)
        - Media packet, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 14)
        - Notes on the future of the NSCD, circa 1982 (Box 112, Folder 15)
        - Miscellany: notes, phone messages, addresses, undated (Box 112, Folder 16)
        - Project Director Barbara Sprung
          - "A Brief Introduction to the Non-Sexist Child Development Project," typescript, undated (Box 112, Folder 17)
          - Article drafts, 1975-77 (Box 112, Folder 18)
          - "Curriculum Suggestion for a Non-Sexist Approach to Early Childhood Teaching," typescript, undated (Box 113, Folder 1)
          - Consulting, contract, 1977 (Box 113, Folder 2)
          - Correspondence, 1975-80 (Box 113, Folder 3)
          - Day care notes, undated (Box 113, Folder 4)
          - Chancellor's Advisory Committee for the State of New York: meeting materials, correspondence, discussion papers, reports, proposals, memoranda, minutes, and miscellany, 1974-76 (Box 113, Folder 5-13)
        - Contacts: correspondence, printed material, notes, 1977-79
          - General, foreign, Head Start, and minority (Box 113, Folder 16-19)
          - National, New York City, publishers, sex/race desegregation centers, and television (Box 114, Folder 1-5)
        - Courses: correspondence, syllabi, outlines, registrations, 1974-76 (Box 114, Folder 6-12)
      - Development
        - Correspondence, funder lists, and presentations, 1972-90 (Box 114, Folder 13-17)
        - Proposals, 1972-81 (includes materials on children's television,, sports, disabilities, domestic violence, and multiculturalism) (Box 114-118)
      - Financial and legal: audit, budgets, income sheets, invoices, reprint requests, price lists, royalty statements, travel vouchers, 1974-79 (Box 118, Folder 6-16)
      - Mailings, 1978-79 (Box 118, Folder 17)
      - Publicity and promotion
        - Advertising material, articles, and proposals, 1977-79 (Box 118, Folder 18-20)
        - Press releases and notes, promotional material, and Public Interest Public Relations correspondence, 1975-82 (Box 119, Folder 1-5)
      - Reports
        - Board of Directors and general, 1973-83 (Box 119, Folder 7-10)
        - To funders and miscellaneous, 1973-80 (Box 120, Folder 1-6)
      - Staff: applications, correspondence, lists, policies, minutes and memoranda, 1976-79 (Box 120, Folder 7-14)
      - Subjects
        - A-B (Box 120, Folder 15-20)
        - B-M (Box 121, Folder 1-16)
        - M-W (Box 122, Folder 1-20)
      - Field testing and related activities
        - Surveys
          - Child Development Project: circa 1974 (Box 122, Folder 21)
          - Child care centers: questionnaires, tabulations, and reports (Box 123, Folder 1-3)
          - Departments of Early Childhood Education: questionnaires, tabulations, and reports (Box 123, Folder 4-6)
      - Materials developed and distributed
        - General (Box 123, Folder 7)
        - Brochures (Box 123, Folder 8)
        - Educat mailing, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 9)
        - "Guidelines for the Development and Evaluation of Unbiased Educational Material," Felicita George, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 10)
        - Curriculum guides: distribution list, 1974-75 (Box 123, Folder 11)
        - Films and filmstrips
          - "A Non-Sexist Curriculum for Early Childhood" filmstrip: contracts, correspondence, sales report, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 12-14)
          - Brochures, leader guides, reviews for films "The Sooner the Better," "The Time Has Come" and "Sugar & Spice: A Film about Non-Sexist Education" (Box 123, Folder 15-17)
          - Copyright authorizations, 1977 (Box 123, Folder 18)
          - Evaluations, circa 1978
            - Correspondence, instructions, and forms (Box 123, Folder 19-20)
            - Nancy Gropper's assessment and teacher responses (Box 124, Folder 1-2)
          - Miscellany (Box 124, Folder 3)
          - Jamil Simon Productions: correspondence and invoices, 1977 (Box 124, Folder 4)
          - Research material (Box 124, Folder 5-6)
          - Royalties and other income: correspondence and cancelled checks, 1978-81 (Box 124, Folder 7)
          - Screening: invitations, mailing, press list, and Letter of Agreement and invoices, PIPR, 1977-79 (Box 124, Folder 8-10)
          - Video notes, undated (Box 124, Folder 11)
        - Resource photos
          - Men in the Nurturing Role: estimates, releases, miscellany, 1974 (Box 124, Folder 12-14)
            [see also SERIES V. AUDIOVISUAL]
          - Resource Photos for Mainstreaming: brochures, descriptions, and miscellany, 1978, undated (Box 124, Folder 15-16)
            [see also Project R.E.E.D.]
        - Toys: includes material from Milton Bradley, evaluations, and correspondence re: Male Nurturing Puzzles, 1974-82 (Box 125, Folder 1-5)
        - Training manuals: description, circa 1978 (Box 125, Folder 6)
        - Publications
          - The WAA Guide to Non-Sexist Early Childhood Education 1974 (Box 125, Folder 7)